- Everywhere we go
- Everywhere were go
- People wanna know
- Who we are
- So we tell them
- We are Artillery
- Mighty fine Artillery
- Everywhere we go
- People wanna know
- Who we are
- First platoon, Company B
- We're the best you'll ever see
- Company B Artillery
To the left, to the left
To the left, right, left
- Everywhere we go
- People wanna know
Keep up the pace.
Left, left, left, right, left
One, two, three, four, left, right, left
- Hear the news?
- I died?
Five perfect inspections in a row.
- Everybody's going in town tonight.
- Not me.
- You're not?
- No way.
In the last 24 hours,
I've cleaned two latrines,
policed the parade grounds,
run an obstacle course,
and painted the flag pole.
My back is killing me.
What used to be simple little blisters
on my hands and my feet
are now bleeding sores.
Now, as much as I hate
this little bunk,
when I lay my head on this pillow,
it will not move until morning.
Ten-hut!
Gentlemen, there will be
no night on the town tonight.
This platoon will be in full field gear
at 1 800 hours
ready for a little speed march.
Carry on.
Did you have any idea
that he was gonna run?
- No, of course I didn't.
- Where is he, Nancy?
Don't you think I'd tell you if I knew?
I swore I'd never get involved
with a soldier,
- and I never should have.
- You just can't fall out of love.
Hello?
Hi.
Yes.
Why?
No.
- Police.
- I've gotta go.
Yes, but--
All right.
Are you Nancy Lamont?
- Yes.
- We're looking for Private Hughes.
He's absent without leave.
- Do you know where he is?
- No.
- Have you heard from him?
A warrant's out for his arrest, ma'am.
Know what could happen
for aiding and abetting a fugitive?
I told you I don't know where he is.
- Check the bedroom.
- Just a minute.
- Do you have a search warrant.
- Mind your own business, miss.
- It's okay, Charlene.
- No, it's not okay.
Either you show me your warrant
or you get out.
Or you'll do what?
Get me the police. Emergency.
Let's go.
Thank you, Charlene.
Who was that on the phone?
- Just a friend.
- It was Chris, wasn't it?
Did he tell you where he is?
Nancy,
Chris is in very serious trouble.
- Not if they can't find him.
- Don't kid yourself.
You've simply got to tell me
where he is.
He'll ruin his life.
Hello, Chris.
- Nancy?
- Yeah.
I kind of halfway figured.
Well, she's a bright girl.
She cares for you.
She'd rather see you lead a full life
than an empty one or no life at all.
- I really screwed up this time, didn't I?
- You panicked.
Yeah. Yeah, I panicked.
Parker didn't show up.
I mean, let's face it,
I don't have a chance.
And I'll tell you something else.
I'm scared to death.
The old man was right.
I never will put it together.
Well, your father
wasn't always hot stuff.
He got his hands on a little money
and used it to make more money.
He was always good at that,
but he wasn't always hot stuff.
He had to kind of grow
into it like everybody else.
You know,
sometimes you look at a person
and you think that person
was always what you're looking at,
and that's not necessarily so.
I mean, just take me.
I wasn't always a lawyer.
I wasn't always successful.
I was once
just a little brown-headed kid,
and like all the other little kids
I knew,
I was just trying to do what I was
supposed to do and stay out of trouble.
Sometimes I'd miss, sometimes l--
Sometimes I'd miss pretty bad.
I spent two years
in the fourth grade.
You don't have to tell
that around too much.
Provide Private Hughes
with the appropriate government issue.
Then escort him to his cell.
I'll inform General Connors
he's been taken into custody.
That he turned himself in,
and inform your men
to keep their hands
and batons off him.
He'll be well taken care of, sir.
Major, I'd like to bounce a couple
things off you. It'll just take a minute.
You know,
I saw in the coroner's report
that Lieutenant Walters
had a jagged cut across his hand,
one that could not have been caused
by a bayonet.
- Did you notice that?
- Yes, sir.
- How do you think he got it?
- I haven't the faintest idea.
Well, did you see anything in that room
that could have caused a cut like that?
No.
I think Private Hughes is being framed
for Lieutenant Walter's murder.
- That would take quite a lot of doing.
- Well,
take Private Hughes' bayonet,
for instance, the murder weapon.
Isn't it possible that somebody
took it out of his footlocker,
killed Lieutenant Walters,
and then put it back?
Possible, but unlikely.
Not in front of
a whole platoon of men.
Don't all bayonets look
pretty much the same?
Yes, sir.
Well, then someone could've switched
the bayonet
that was in Chris' footlocker
with the murder weapon,
say at the time his footlocker
was searched.
All that means
- is that it wasn't a frame.
- How is that?
Because I'm the one
who searched Private Hughes' locker.
Well, so much for theories.
Unless, of course we discover that you
had a motive to kill Lieutenant Walters.
- I didn't.
- Good. Good.
Because as I recall,
you don't have an alibi, either.
I'll see you, major.
Excuse me.
- I'm looking for Sergeant Parker.
- He's not here.
When do you expect him?
In about 30 days.
- He went on leave this morning.
- He went on leave?
He's supposed to testify
in the Chris Hughes case.
He's my star witness.
Hell, he's my only witness.
- I'm sorry.
- You know where he went?
- No.
- I talked to Sergeant Parker yesterday
and he never said one damn word
about going anywhere.
Now, I wanna know who arranged this
leave and how it processed so quickly.
Listen, I don't have to answer
any of your questions.
I don't even know who you are.
My name's Ben Matlock,
and you'll answer my questions here
or in front of General Connors.
Well, Parker was due leave,
Parker asked for leave,
and I gave Parker leave. Here.
I processed the paperwork myself.
Go ahead. Take a look.
Move it out!
All right, gentlemen,
through and back.
The record is
two hours and 1 7 minutes.
And there'll be weekend passes
if you break it.
Move them out.
Left face!
Double time, march!
You'd think after Bobby died here
with Walters,
they'd pick something else
to torture us.
- This where it happened?
- Same place, same drill, everything.
- I twisted my ankle.
- Here, I'll give you a hand.
No, you go ahead. Go ahead.
I'll catch up.
Come on.
Wait a minute.
I thought I heard something.
Nothing.
Let's hurry it up.
Good night, ladies.
Evening ladies.
- Evening, Danny.
- Hey, Mr. Matlock.
Oh, mister, huh?
I think we know one another
well enough now. Call me Ben.
Okay, Ben.
I got another hot flash for you.
Yeah?
Poker game in the back room,
same guys,
just like nothing ever happened.
Old habits are hard to break,
especially the bad ones.
Danny, is there anything
about what happened
that you didn't tell
the investigating officer,
anything that you or he
may have dismissed
as insignificant or immaterial?
No, I don't think so.
You mind going over it
one more time?
Well, about closing time,
the Hughes kid busts in here
looking like he just crawled out
of the woods, which, in fact, he had.
Anyway, I tried to stop him
from going in the back room,
but he was real determined.
I was cleaning up just like I am now,
so I thought, ''What the hell.
Who cares?''
I just wanted to go home.
- Then what happened?
- Well, I heard a lot of yelling
and a bunch of scuffling
like a fight was going on.
Then everything got real quiet.
About a minute later, the kid left.
About two minutes later so did I.
The men in the back room
just kept playing cards?
Yeah.
What?
I do remember something.
When I clean up, I like to scrub
the bar down real good,
so I take off the ashtrays
and I stack them over there.
But when I came back to work
the day after the killing,
there was one ashtray right there.
- Anything in it?
- Yeah.
The butt of a cigar and some ashes.
Any of those guys smoke a cigar?
As far as I know, Captain Campbell,
sometimes Major Hamilton.
Hey, Danny, scotch on the rocks.
So much for getting out of here.
You go on home.
I'll tell them you left.
Hey, thanks, Ben.
Danny!
Danny's gone home.
Who's winning?
He is.
Four-handed poker.
Can't build up much of a pot.
Can't play high-Iow
or any split games.
One of our regulars dropped out.
You know,
one of the most puzzling things
about Lieutenant Walters' murder
is that little black book.
Why would the murderer bother
to take the record
of who owed what to whom
in a nice innocent poker game?
Who's keeping track
now that Lieutenant Walters is gone?
I am.
What, you just zero everybody out
and start over?
We just took up where we left off.
We've got a pretty fair idea
of who owed what to whom.
I'm not much of a poker player.
I mean, once in a while.
In games that I've seen you just
put your money down at the beginning
and pick up whatever's left
at the end.
I never heard of players
running tabs.
We're friends.
I'm sure you are.
I just never heard of that.
Running tabs on a poker game.
It's strange. It's very strange.
- Hey, I've seen you in here before.
- That's right.
Come on over to the table.
I'll buy you a drink.
Well, that's very nice of you,
but not just now, okay?
You don't want a drink?
Thanks anyway.
- Is this seat taken?
- Jim. No.
Look, I'm sorry I'm late.
No, you're just in time.
I've been under attack.
Well, I can see why.
Here's to new friends.
Friends.
I thought you weren't thirsty.
What's it to you?
Come on.
My money's as good as his.
- Take your hands off me.
- You heard her.
Just get in line, Jack.
Back off.
No problem.
- Okay.
- Okay. Hey, okay.
I hope she's worth it.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
That guy's got a hell of a right.
Yeah, I'm okay. I think.
Good.
- Look, I'm sorry about all that.
- No, no. It's not your fault.
I'll tell you what. There's a nice
little diner down the street.
The least I could do for my hero
is to buy him a cup of coffee.
I'll tell you my hard luck stories
and you can tell me yours.
Okay.
Good news.
We went on field exercises last night
with Lieutenant Lynch.
He took us to the same place
Walters used to take them.
So, when I heard that, I doubled back,
and you know what I saw?
I saw Lieutenant Lynch
and two civilians unloading packages
out of a four-wheeler
and hiding them in the truck.
Now, when we were going
back to the post,
I heard Lynch say something about
he had to stop off at the supply depot
before taking the truck
back to the motor pool.
I couldn't follow him.
I had to go on guard duty.
Ben, this platoon sergeant
loves to hate me.
- What was in the packages?
- I don't know.
Well--
All right, I'll find out, but Ben,
I have not slept in 36 hours.
I don't think we can wait.
All right.
Supply depot tonight.
I'd like a rum
and whatever cola you've got.
- How are the tennis lessons going?
- I just want a drink, okay?
Ms. Campbell,
I'm glad you could make it.
How have you been?
Not so great, thanks to you.
I'm sorry, I really am.
At the time I had no idea you'd
required so much medical attention.
for broken bones and contusions
I've never understood why a woman
stays with a man who beats her.
stays with a man who didn't.
You're a real piece of work,
Ms. Campbell,
your husband abuses you,
you have an affair with a man
that everybody
in the next ten miles despises.
He was nice enough to me.
Why did your husband and the others
play cards with him?
I don't know.
But did you have any other friends,
civilian friends?
- He had no friends, period.
- Except you.
I guess I was enough.
And your husband
really didn't know?
What do you think?
Paula.
Come on, let's go.
Would you please excuse me?
It must be time
for my tongue lashing.
Stay away from her.
Colonel McRae
wants to ship this stuff.
And it's gotta go out tonight.
Soldier.
- Which one of you is Johnson?
- I am.
I'm Lieutenant Hudson.
Don't you salute a superior officer?
Yes sir.
Sergeant wants to see you
at the motor pool on the double
and take your buddy with you.
- But, sir--
- Soldier, I just gave you an order.
Now, both of you, move it.
On the double.
You move, you're dead.
We've got you on trespassing,
impersonating an officer,
and destroying government property.
It's all a mistake.
- You'll say, ''sir,'' when you talk to me.
- It's all a mistake, sir.
Well, let's try it again.
Why were you in the supply depot,
private?
I was looking for drugs, sir.
What made you think
there were drugs?
I heard some talk in the mess hall.
What kind of talking, private.
Something about shipping cocaine.
- Who was talking?
- I don't know. Just some guys, sir.
So you took their word for it,
snuck into the depot,
impersonated an officer,
started tearing boxes.
Yes, sir.
Do you think I'm an idiot, private?
Do you?
- No, sir.
- Think again.
Start all over again. Ten-hut.
At ease.
I want this man released
immediately.
We caught him trespassing
and destroying property, sir.
He's an associate of Mr. Matlock's.
He was placed on this post
undercover.
Why was I not informed of this, sir?
You just were.
For your information,
I wasn't impersonating an officer.
I am an officer.
First Lieutenant Tyler Hudson,
283243245,
United States Army Reserve.
Ben, they're shipping cocaine
out of the supply depot.
It's uncut. It's high-grade.
I tasted it, I saw it, I can't prove it,
and I can guarantee you whatever
was there, it's long gone by now.
Damn.
How you doing with the hearing?
Hearing's over.
Court-martial starts tomorrow.
Does that answer your question?
Major Hamilton,
I show you the government's
Exhibit Number 4
and ask if you recognise it.
Yes, sir, I do.
That's my tag, my initials.
Well, counsel for the defence
has already stipulated
that this is the weapon
that killed Lieutenant Walters.
Major, would you please tell the court
where it was found?
- In Private Hughes' footlocker.
- Thank you.
No further questions.
Who found this bayonet
in Private Hughes' footlocker, major?
- I did.
- Have it checked for fingerprints?
Yes, sir, none were found.
None on the blade?
- That's right.
- How about the handle?
None there either.
Didn't that strike you as odd?
Didn't strike me at all, sir.
I mean, why would Private Hughes
wipe his fingerprints off his bayonet
if he was gonna put it
in his footlocker?
Objection. Calls for speculation.
Let me put it this way. Doesn't
the fact that the bayonet was found
in Private Hughes' footlocker
with no fingerprints
suggest that someone
other than Private Hughes put it there?
Objection. That's the same question.
Sustained.
No further questions.
I call Sergeant Owens to the stand.
Yes, sir. I work in the supply depot.
And where were you on the night
of January 1 1 ?
In the depot. I remember it
because there was a big shipment
that was due out on the 1 2th and a lot
of paperwork that needed to be done.
Just how late did you work?
Till about 2245.
That's when Colonel McCrea
came in and relieved me.
You had to walk
past the officers' club
to get to your car that night.
Is that correct?
Yes, sir. And as I was passing by,
I heard this door slam.
That's what made me look up,
and I saw Private Hughes
come out of the building and--
- Well, he was running away.
- Thank you. No further questions.
Sergeant Owens,
you dropped out of school
to join the Army, is that correct?
Yes, sir.
When you send out a big shipment
like you did the night of the murder,
what kind of paperwork's involved?
Transmittal letters and documents
have to be prepared,
inventory's revised, telexes have to be
sent to bases receiving the materials,
that sort of thing.
That sounds complicated.
You do it by yourself?
Yes, sir. I'm just about the only one
on the base that can.
I think that's terrific.
No further questions.
- What was that all about?
- I think I'm on to something.
Sir, the government rests.
Is the defence ready, Mr. Matlock?
We call Colonel McCrea
to the stand.
You left the poker game
and went back to the supply depot
to relieve your assistant,
Sergeant Owens. Is that correct?
Yes, sir.
Was anybody in the supply depot
with you after Sergeant Owens left?
No, sir. I was alone.
- Your Honour, at this time--
- Mr. Matlock--
Major Orlando, surely you can't
object to these papers
before you even know
what they are.
Mr. Matlock, in a military court,
the judge is addressed as ''sir,''
not ''Your Honour.''
Excuse me, sir.
Sir,
at this time, defence
would like to introduce into evidence
these telex messages sent from
the supply depot here at Fort Simpson
on the night of January 1 1th.
Now, will you read the times
these telex messages were sent?
According to the time codes,
224 7, 2258, 2308 and 231 5.
- Who sent them?
- It's not indicated.
Well, you just told us
that you were in the supply depot alone
at the times indicated
on these messages,
so I guess that must mean
that you sent them.
- I suppose so.
- Did you send them?
Yes, I sent them.
Defence Exhibit B
is a telex machine.
Actually, it is the telex machine
from the supply depot
that was used
to send those messages
all set and ready to go.
Now, colonel,
why don't you just come over here
and show us how you sent them.
I just type them.
It sure looks more complicated
than that to me.
Don't be modest. Just step down,
come over here, and show us how.
I can't.
I don't know how the telex works.
Someone else must've sent
the messages. I don't remember.
Yes, you do.
Sergeant Owens
sent those messages, didn't he.
No, no. He'd already gone.
No, he hadn't. He didn't leave
the supply depot at 2245.
He was there at least until 231 5.
- Wasn't he?
- No.
Which means he could not have seen
Private Hughes
leave the officers' club
at the time of the murder, could he?
- What's higher, a straight or a flush?
- A straight.
Full house or four of a kind?
Objection. Relevancy.
Colonel McCrea has told us that
he was playing poker with the victim
less than an hour
before the murder.
Now, Your Honour--
Excuse me, sir--
That fact alone
makes this line of questioning relevant.
- Overruled.
- Thank you.
That is what you said,
isn't it, colonel?
That you and three other men
were playing poker
with Lieutenant Walters
in a back room of the officers' club?
Yes.
In a room with a wall mirror.
A person playing poker at that table
could've seen the hands of one,
maybe two of his opponents.
I gotta tell you something,
colonel.
That's some strange game.
No further questions.
No further question.
Colonel McCrea, you're dismissed.
Sir, I'd like to request
a brief recess at this time
for a consultation with an associate.
Ten minutes.
I can't do it.
- What do you mean you can't do it?
- Jim Lynch is my friend.
Jim Lynch is a witness.
He's got to take the stand.
I don't care
what your relationship is.
- This is so hard.
- Charlene, you're a professional.
I'm asking you
to keep faith with our client.
You know what profession
I feel like I'm in right now?
All right, I'll question him,
but you've gotta be there for details.
I'll do it.
Charlene, I know how you feel,
but as lawyers,
we've got to defend that boy.
Is the defence ready?
Sir, defence calls
Lieutenant Lynch to the stand
and my associate, Charlene Matlock,
will question him.
Call Lieutenant Lynch.
Lieutenant Lynch.
Lieutenant Lynch,
you knew the victim, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
In fact, you served together
during the invasion in Grenada.
- Isn't that so?
- That's correct.
Isn't it true that Lieutenant Walters
was blackmailing you
for cowardice under fire?
No. Absolutely not.
And that he was forcing you
to participate against your will
in certain criminal activities?
That's ridiculous.
Jim,
I know that you confided in me
out of friendship
and that you never expected the things
you told me to go any further.
- I have no idea what--
- Jim,
if you don't testify, my father's
gonna put me on the stand
and force me to tell what you said.
Did Lieutenant Walters
force you to participate
in certain criminal activities?
Yes.
Would you please tell the court
what these activities were?
Lieutenant...
Lieutenant Walters would purchase
large amounts of cocaine,
which he then distributed
through Army channels.
Was anybody else involved?
Colonel McCrea, Major Hamilton,
Captain Campbell,
Sergeant Owens, two civilians,
among others.
And just how
did the scheme work?
Lieutenant Walters or I would
take a platoon out on manoeuvres,
where we would secretly
meet with the two civilians.
They would provide us
with the cocaine,
which we would then take back
to the supply depot.
And Colonel McCrea
would then make sure
that it got to our contacts at posts
throughout the country.
And weren't the poker games
that you five took part in
really just business meetings?
A way of getting together
to place orders
and exchange large sums of money
without arousing suspicion?
- Yes.
- And wasn't the little black book
that was taken
when Lieutenant Walters was killed
actually a record
of these drug transactions?
- Yes.
- Isn't that why he was murdered,
because of the drug trafficking?
I have no idea.
I left early on that evening,
so I wouldn't know about that.
Where did you go after you left?
To a bar.
I was there till about one.
Thank you, Lieutenant.
No further questions.
Sergeant, place this man
under arrest.
Colonel McCrea, Major Hamilton,
Captain Campbell,
and Sergeant Owens
are to be placed
in arrested quarters.
This court is recessed until 0900
hours tomorrow.
Well, what do you think?
Nice piece of work.
We're not close to acquittal yet,
are we?
- Not yet.
- Not yet?
Not yet.
But there's an old rule
in the drug game--
Follow the money.
- My husband's not home.
- I know.
I believe he's busy not answering
questions over at the post.
I came to see you.
Why don't you go in and watch TV?
Mommy will be in,
in a few minutes, okay?
Beautiful little girl.
Yes, she is.
Sometimes I think
she's the only reason
I bother getting up in the morning.
She's also the reason you dropped
the divorce, isn't she?
What divorce?
The one you filed two years ago.
It may not be public knowledge,
but it is public record.
Bill demanded custody.
Swore he'd get it.
Captain Campbell a wife beater?
No one within 1 00 miles
would believe that, so I backed off.
And you got even by having an affair
with a man he hated.
That is where it started, isn't it?
What do you mean?
Mrs. Campbell, you visited
Lieutenant Walters' grave
three or four times a week.
That's not an act of vengeance.
That's an act of love.
I really loved him.
Some information
has come to my attention
that leads me to believe that...
your husband killed him.
Hi, Jim.
I hear you've been granted
immunity.
Yeah. I've just given
the CID my statement.
What happens now?
Dishonourable discharge.
I'm sorry.
Actually, it feels kind of good.
Don't tell me where you've been.
Just tell me you got the bank records.
I got them.
This court will come to order.
Mr. Matlock, next witness, please.
Sir, we call Captain William Campbell
to the stand.
I understand that you
and Major Hamilton
and Lieutenants Lynch and Walters
and Colonel McCrea
were all in a back room
of the officers' club
on the night Lieutenant Walters
was murdered. Is that correct?
- Yes, sir.
- And I understand that all of you
were engaged in a conspiracy
to buy and sell cocaine.
Is that correct?
''On the advice of my attorney,
I regretfully and respectfully
decline to answer
on the constitutional grounds,
protecting my rights
against self-incrimination.''
Sir,
at this time, I'd like to enter
into evidence these bank records.
Maybe you can answer
this question for us, captain.
This is a copy of a statement
from one of your savings accounts.
- Is that correct?
- Yes, sir.
And on January 1 2th,
you deposited 1 5,000 dollars.
Is that correct?
- Yes, sir.
- Where did the money come from?
''On the advice of my attorney,
I regretfully and respectfully
- decline to answer on--''
- We get the picture.
Sir,
at this time, I'd like to enter
into evidence the bank records
of Major Hamilton, Lieutenant Lynch,
and Colonel McCrea.
As you can see, over the past six
months, each of these three men
have deposited exactly
300,000 dollars.
I call your attention now to the deposits
made on January 1 2th.
Each of the other three conspirators
deposited 7,500 dollars.
You deposited 1 5,000 dollars.
Why did you get twice as much?
I decline to answer.
You know what I think?
I think you got 7,500,
just like the others,
but then you took
Lieutenant Walters' share as well
because you're the one
who killed him.
Objection.
Counsel is arguing the evidence.
Sustained.
Just examine the witness,
please, Mr. Matlock.
Yes, sir. You smoke a cigar,
don't you, captain?
Yes.
You smoked one that night
in the back room, didn't you?
I don't know. Probably.
And you smoked another one
at the bar after everyone left.
I don't think so, Mr. Matlock.
You smoked a cigar
while you waited for Major Hamilton
to return with a certain bayonet,
and you left the butt of that cigar
in an ashtray on the bar, didn't you?
No.
Once you had the bayonet,
you went back into that room,
where Lieutenant Walters
was finishing his bookkeeping.
You went into that room
and you killed him.
You stabbed Lieutenant Walters
to death with that bayonet, didn't you?
None of that is true.
You know,
there are a couple of things
about this case that are really puzzling.
I mean, the coroner said
that Lieutenant Walters
had a raw abrasion on his hand
that was not caused by the bayonet.
How do you suppose he got that?
I haven't the faintest idea.
And the blood on the seat
of the overturned chair
indicates that Lieutenant Walters
was sitting with his back to the door
when he was stabbed.
He should've fallen forward,
but his body was found
on the floor facing the door.
How do you suppose
that happened?
- I haven't the faintest idea.
- I do.
See, I think Lieutenant Walters
was stabbed in a seated position,
and as his killer turned to leave,
with his last breath,
Lieutenant Walters rose up
and grabbed the man from behind.
You know what he grabbed?
I haven't the faintest idea.
The thing that cut his hand.
The chain.
The chain that holds the dog tags.
Isn't it true that on January 1 4th,
you had your wife
take a gold chain
to a local jeweller for repairs?
According to this work order,
this gold chain
that ordinarily holds your dog tags.
I had a chain fixed.
- What does that prove?
- Nothing.
But if Lieutenant Walters
pulled this chain so hard
that he broke it and cut his hand,
I'll bet you've got a pretty good cut
on your neck as well.
You mind opening your shirt for us?
Yes.
Yes, yes, I do mind.
You can open your shirt here,
or the MPs will open it for you
back at the stockade.
We...
We drew straws for it.
Colonel McCrea and Major Hamilton
are just as guilty as I am.
Sir, in light of this new evidence
and testimony,
defence moves for a dismissal.
The court looks favourable
on your motion.
Major Orlando, any objections?
No, sir. No objections.
The charges against Private Hughes
are dismissed.
Thanks.
You came through for me.
Why don't you
give your father a call?
Why would I do that?
Show him the Army
made a man out of you.
Might set a good example for him.
Thank you.
Thank you, Charlene.
Well, I guess
I don't have to ask who won.
Tyler, there's an old tradition
we jailhouse lawyers like to practise
after winning
a particularly difficult case.
- There is?
- Oh, yeah.
Give me five!
www.tvsubtitles.net